University of Connecticut 1998.0189
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
University of Connecticut, President's Office Records [John T. Casteen III, 1985-1989]
1981-1990.
1998.0189
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
42.5 Linear feet
John T. Casteen III was inaugurated as the University of Connecticut's eleventh president on October 12, 1985.
University of Connecticut. President's Office.
History
John T. Casteen III was inaugurated as the University of Connecticut's eleventh president on 12 October 1985. After earning his B.A., M.A. and Ph. D. degrees in English from the University of Virginia, Dr. Casteen went on to become a professor of English at that University, as well as serving as its Dean of Admissions. He also taught at the University of California at Berkeley, the University of Delaware, and at Maryland State College. He was both an adjunct professor of English at Virginia Commonwealth University, and Secretary of Education for the Commonwealth of Virginia from 1982-1985.
Among President Casteen's goals for the University of Connecticut was the reforming of the undergraduate program with a focus on a common core of learning and, at the same time, the expansion of the graduate program. His intention was to foster growth within the faculty and staff and build up resources and facilities equal to sound academic plans for the future.
Despite state budget cuts during his tenure, President Casteen's administration managed to prevent layoffs and keep program reduction to a minimum. The physical plant was improved with monies earned from bond authorizations, and improvements included renovations to Hall, Arjona, and Monteith buildings, as well as to the Pharmacy building. Other improvements included lab construction and renovations, a new administrative services building at the Health Center in Farmington, and construction of the Gampel Pavilion. In addition, President Casteen's administration developed new sources of financing for projects such as the telecommunications system, and increased private funding for the University as well.
In 1985 and 1986, a new curriculum was adopted, which put an emphasis on general education requirements. The international study programs were developed, with particular focus on Poland. Research and development activity nearly doubled in his five years as president. Casteen also supported the development of the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, to house the Library's Archives & Special Collections, two academic centers, and a small conference center.
In addition to physical plant and academic growth, UConn saw a new, wider diversity of minority groups among the school's leadership, an achievement of Casteen's personal goal for both quality and equality within the University.
On 9 March 1990, President Casteen announced he was leaving the University of Connecticut to take the presidency at the University of Virginia, his alma mater.
Scope and Content
The records in this collection are the files of the President's office during John T. Casteen's administration from 1985-1990. The documents include correspondence, reports, financial and administrative records, as well as materials pertaining to his inauguration and plaques and mementos accumulated during his tenure as president.
Arrangement
Series I: Inauguration ( undated ) contains materials from President Casteen's inauguration, and includes invitation lists, records regarding preparation for the ceremony, certificates and letters sent by other universities, thank you letters, and the president's inaugural address.
Series II: Memorabilia ( undated ) contains various certificates, plaques, and medals received by Dr. Casteen during his tenure as University President.
Series III-VII: Within each of the five chronological series, the records are arranged under the following subheadings: University Files (Red Files); State Government Files (Blue Files); Federal Government Files (Green Files); Organization Files (Black Files); and Educational Associations (Yellow Files). University Files contains University related programs and policies, financial reports, correspondence with academic departments, lawsuits and grievances, and meeting minutes, as well as files dealing with subjects such as transportation, safety, exchange programs, and racism. State Government Files contains materials pertaining to interaction with the State of Connecticut, and includes audit reports, correspondence with the Board of Governors and the Governor's office, and State University System and legislative materials. Federal Government Files includes Congressional and Senate inquiries, federal law requirements for public institutions, and federal legislative materials. Organization Files contains files on other colleges and universities, as well as on businesses such as Shell Corporation and Travelers Insurance. Education Associations includes files on the New England Association of Schools and Colleges, Campus Compact, and the Council of Presidents. Within each subheading, files are arranged alphabetically by folder heading.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to the University, its history, administration, faculty, staff and students. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Bibliography
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
The President's Office Records, 1985-1989, were transferred in yearly accessions from the President's Office to the University Archives.
Administrative Records.; Audio cassettes.; Audio visual materials.; College presidents—Connecticut.; Correspondence.; Financial Records.; Fliers. [printed matter]; Minutes.; Notebooks.; Notes.; Photocopies.; Photographs.; Press releases.; Publications.; Speeches.; Universities and colleges—Administration.; Universities.; University of Connecticut. Office of the President.; University of Connecticut—Presidents.; Videocassettes.
- Series I: Inauguration, undated
  - Attending Dignitaries/ Delegates (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Banner-Gram, Avery Point Campus (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Ceremony and Speech (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Diskettes (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - Halvorson Speech (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Inaugural Address - Casteen (Box 1:, Folder 7)
  - Inaugural Symposium (October 11) (Box 1:, Folder 8)
  - Inauguration Committee (Box 1:, Folder 9)
  - Invitations (Box 1:, Folder 10)
  - Invitation Accepts - Return Correspondence, Information, and Tickets (Box 1:, Folder 11)
  - Letters Received, Colleges and Universities (including UConn) (Box 1:, Folder 12)
  - Letters to Guests (Box 1:, Folder 13)
  - Letters to Participants (Box 1:, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Articles (Box 1:, Folder 15)
  - Programs (Box 1:, Folder 16)
  - Thank You Letters, Re: Congratulatory Certificates (Box 1:, Folder 17)
  - Robert Wood Speech (Keynote Speaker) (Box 1:, Folder 18)
  - Congratulatory Certificates (Box 2:, Folder 19)
- Series II: Memorabilia, undated, 1988-1989
  - Certificate: The Elementary and Middle School Principals' Association of Connecticut President's Award (Box 3:, Folder 20)
  - Medal: The Aristoteleio University of Thessaloniki, 1989 February 20 (Box 3:, Folder 21)
  - Plaque: Firat University, Elazig, Turkey, 1988 April 26 (Box 3:, Folder 22)
  - Plaque: Firat University, Elazig, Turkey, 1989 March 3 (Box 3:, Folder 23)
  - Plaque: Peace at Home/Peace in the World: Compliments of Mr. Bulend Ulusu, Prime Minister of the Republic of Turkey (Box 3:, Folder 24)
  - Plaque: Youth Goodwill Mission of the Republic of China: All Men Are Brothers (Box 3:, Folder 25)
- Series III:, 1985
  - University Files (Red Files)
    - Academic Affairs (Box 4:, Folder 26)
    - Admissions Requirements (Box 4:, Folder 27)
    - Admissions Reports (Box 4:, Folder 28)
    - Affirmative Action Program (Box 4:, Folder 29-30)
    - Afro-American Cultural Center (Box 4:, Folder 31)
    - Agriculture, College of (Box 4:, Folder 32)
    - Agriculture, College of: Richardson Property, Woodstock (Box 4:, Folder 33)
    - AIDS (Box 4:, Folder 34)
    - Alcohol Policy (Box 4:, Folder 35)
    - Allied Health: Accreditation (Box 4:, Folder 36)
    - Animal Care (Box 4:, Folder 37)
    - Annual Reports (Box 4:, Folder 38)
    - Anonymous Letters: Van Kruiningen (Box 4:, Folder 39)
    - Assistant to President: David L. Kimball (Box 4:, Folder 40)
    - Athletics (Box 4:, Folder 41-44)
    - Attorney (Box 4:, Folder 45)
    - Auditor
      - Activity Reports, June 30 and December 31 (Box 4:, Folder 46)
      - Alleged Malfeasance (Box 4:, Folder 47)
      - Charter (Box 4:, Folder 48)
      - Health Center (see also: Health Center films) (Box 4:, Folder 49)
      - Office Matters: organization, budget (Box 4:, Folder 50)
      - Personal Computer Acquisitions (Box 4:, Folder 51)
      - Personal Matters (Box 4:, Folder 52)
      - Research Foundation (Box 4:, Folder 53)
    - Biobehavioral Science: Funding and Search (Box 4:, Folder 54)
    - Biotechnology (Box 4:, Folder 55)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 4:, Folder 56)
    - Budget (Box 4:, Folder 57-58)
    - Burke, Fred (Box 4:, Folder 59)
    - Bursar (Box 4:, Folder 60)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 4:, Folder 61)
    - Center for Instructional Media (Box 4:, Folder 62)
    - Classified Staff (Box 4:, Folder 63)
    - Co-Op (Box 4:, Folder 64)
    - Cooperative Education (Box 4:, Folder 65)
    - Core Curriculum (Box 4:, Folder 66)
    - Development (Box 4:, Folder 67)
    - Economics: Fred Carstensen (Box 4:, Folder 68)
    - Education, School of (Box 4:, Folder 69)
    - Education, School of: Goodkind (Box 4:, Folder 70)
    - Emeritus Faculty (Box 4:, Folder 71)
    - Engineering Department (Box 4:, Folder 72)
    - Exchange Programs: Poland, Yugoslavia (Box 4:, Folder 73)
    - Extended and Continuing Education (Box 4:, Folder 74)
    - Facilities, Offices of (Box 5:, Folder 75)
    - Faculty Alumni Center (Box 5:, Folder 76)
    - Faculty Dependents' Tuition (Box 5:, Folder 77)
    - Family Studies (Box 5:, Folder 78)
    - Finance and Administration (Box 5:, Folder 79)
      - Endowment, South Africa (Box 5:, Folder 80)
      - Financial Aid (Box 5:, Folder 81)
      - Richardson Property (Box 5:, Folder 82)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 5:, Folder 83)
    - Graduate School (Box 5:, Folder 84-87)
    - Gant, Ed and Margaret (Box 5:, Folder 88)
    - History Department (Box 5:, Folder 89)
    - Health Center (Box 5:, Folder 90-93)
    - Health Center: John Dempsey Hospital Reorganization (Box 5:, Folder 94-95)
    - Health Center: Uncas on Thames (Box 5:, Folder 96)
    - Honors Program (Box 5:, Folder 97)
    - Hurricane Gloria (Box 5:, Folder 98)
    - Institute of Material Science (Box 5:, Folder 99)
    - Institutional Relations (Box 5:, Folder 100)
    - Institutional Research, Office of (Box 5:, Folder 101)
    - Institutional Programs (Box 5:, Folder 102)
    - Inventory (Box 5:, Folder 103)
    - Landfill Report (Box 5:, Folder 104)
    - Latin American Studies, Center for (Box 5:, Folder 105)
    - Law School (Box 5:, Folder 106)
    - Law School: Dedication, 1983-1985 (Box 5:, Folder 107)
    - Law School: Fundraising (Box 5:, Folder 108)
    - Law School: Renovations (Box 5:, Folder 109)
    - Liberal Arts and Sciences (Box 5:, Folder 110)
    - Library (Box 5:, Folder 111-112)
    - Master Plan (Box 5:, Folder 113)
    - Medicine, School of (Box 5:, Folder 114)
    - Medieval Studies (Box 5:, Folder 115)
    - Merit Increases (Box 5:, Folder 116)
    - Minorities (Box 5:, Folder 117)
    - Minority Center for Academic Programs (Box 5:, Folder 118)
    - Museum of Art, William Benton (Box 5:, Folder 119)
    - Museum of Natural History (Box 5:, Folder 120)
    - Music Department (Box 5:, Folder 121)
    - Newspaper Visits (Box 5:, Folder 122)
    - NERAC (Box 5:, Folder 123)
    - Northwood Apartments (Box 5:, Folder 124)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 5:, Folder 125)
    - Office Coverage (Box 5:, Folder 126)
    - Parking (Box 6:, Folder 127)
    - Peace Education (Box 6:, Folder 128)
    - Personnel (Box 6:, Folder 129)
    - Pharmacy, School of (Box 6:, Folder 130)
    - Physics Department (Box 6:, Folder 131)
    - Political Science Department (Box 6:, Folder 132)
    - Policy Statements (Box 6:, Folder 133)
    - President (Box 6:, Folder 134)
    - President's Auto Report (Box 6:, Folder 135)
    - President's Office Renovations (Box 6:, Folder 136)
    - Professional Development Fund (Box 6:, Folder 137)
    - Psychology Department (Box 6:, Folder 138)
    - Public Safety Division (Box 6:, Folder 139)
    - Publications (Box 6:, Folder 140)
    - Puerto Rican Concerns (Box 6:, Folder 141)
    - Racism (Box 6:, Folder 142)
    - Regional Campuses
      - Hartford (Box 6:, Folder 143)
      - Southeastern (Box 6:, Folder 144-145)
      - Stamford (Box 6:, Folder 146)
      - Waterbury (Box 6:, Folder 147)
    - Reorganization (Box 6:, Folder 148)
    - Research and Development Corporation (Box 6:, Folder 149)
    - Research Foundation (Box 6:, Folder 150)
    - ROTC: Air Force (Box 6:, Folder 151)
    - ROTC: Army (Box 6:, Folder 152)
    - Safety (Box 6:, Folder 153)
    - Salaries (Box 6:, Folder 154)
    - Scholarship: Gant (Box 6:, Folder 155)
    - Senate Executive Committee (Box 6:, Folder 156)
    - Social Inquiry (Box 6:, Folder 157)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 6:, Folder 158)
    - South Africa n Students (Box 6:, Folder 159)
    - Special Olympics Proposal (Box 6:, Folder 160)
    - Student Affairs (Box 6:, Folder 161-163)
    - Student Organizations (Box 6:, Folder 164)
    - Telecommunications (Box 6:, Folder 165)
    - Transportation (Box 6:, Folder 166)
    - Tuition (Box 6:, Folder 167)
    - U (Box 6:, Folder 168)
    - UCEPI (Box 6:, Folder 169-174)
    - UConn Foundation (Box 6:, Folder 175)
    - University Relations (Box 6:, Folder 176)
    - Water Resources, Institute of (Box 6:, Folder 177)
    - Women's Center (Box 6:, Folder 178)
    - Women's Studies Program (Box 6:, Folder 179)
  - State Government Files (Blue Files)
    - Administrative Services, Department of (Box 6:, Folder 180)
    - Agriculture (Box 6:, Folder 181)
    - Attorney (Box 6:, Folder 182)
    - Auditor
      - Fiscal Years 1981, 1982, 1983 (Box 6:, Folder 183)
      - Public Services, Institute of (Box 6:, Folder 184)
      - Telephone Credit Card Usage (Box 6:, Folder 185)
      - Torrington Associated Student Government (Box 6:, Folder 186)
      - Undergraduate Student Government (Box 6:, Folder 187)
      - Waterbury Associated Student Government (Box 6:, Folder 188)
    - Board of Governors (Box 6:, Folder 189)
    - CCHE High School Survey (Box 6:, Folder 190)
    - Commission of Human Rights and Opportunities: Affirmative Action Plan (Box 6:, Folder 191)
    - Community College - Regional (Box 6:, Folder 192)
    - Comptroller (Box 6:, Folder 193)
    - Connecticut Conference of Independent Colleges (Box 6:, Folder 194)
    - Connecticut State University: Cooperative Education Program (Box 6:, Folder 195)
    - Connecticut State University: Eastern Connecticut State University (Box 6:, Folder 196)
    - Coordinating Council (Box 6:, Folder 197)
    - Developmental Disabilities (Box 6:, Folder 198)
    - DHE: (Box 7)
      - December (Box 7:, Folder 199-200)
      - November (Box 7:, Folder 201)
      - October (Box 7:, Folder 202)
      - September (Box 7:, Folder 203)
      - August (Box 7:, Folder 204)
      - July (Box 7:, Folder 205)
      - June (Box 7:, Folder 206)
      - May (Box 7:, Folder 207)
      - April (Box 7:, Folder 208)
      - March (Box 7:, Folder 209)
      - February (Box 7:, Folder 210-211)
      - January (Box 7:, Folder 212-213)
      - Fund for Excellence (Box 7:, Folder 214)
      - Independent Colleges, Contracting with (Box 7:, Folder 215)
      - Licensure and Accreditation (Box 7:, Folder 216)
      - Minority Retention (Box 7:, Folder 217)
    - Economic Development, Department of (Box 7:, Folder 218)
    - Governor's Office (Box 7:, Folder 219)
    - Health, Department of (Box 7:, Folder 220)
    - Endowed Chairs (Box 7:, Folder 221)
    - Human Resources Department (Box 7:, Folder 222)
    - Independent Colleges and Universities: Task Force (Box 7:, Folder 223)
    - Jobs for Connecticut's Future (Box 7:, Folder 224)
    - Library, Connecticut State (Box 7:, Folder 225)
    - Legislative Inquiries (Box 7:, Folder 226)
    - Legislative Program Review (Box 7:, Folder 227)
    - Litchfield County Center for Higher Education (Box 7:, Folder 228)
    - Labor, State Department of: Safety (Box 7:, Folder 229)
    - Office of Policy and Management (Box 7:, Folder 230-231)
    - S (Box 7:, Folder 232)
    - Segment Heads (Box 7:, Folder 233)
    - State Police (Box 7:, Folder 234)
    - Telephone and Telecommunications (Box 7:, Folder 235)
    - Transportation, Department of (Box 7:, Folder 236)
  - Federal Government (Green Files)
    - Air Force (Box 8:, Folder 237)
    - Congress and Senate Inquiries, 1984-1988 (Box 8:, Folder 238)
    - Handicap Section 204 (January - September) (Box 8:, Folder 239-240)
    - National Science Foundation Nuclear Regulatory Commission (March - June) (Box 8:, Folder 241)
    - Reauthorization Act (Box 8:, Folder 242)
    - S (Box 8:, Folder 243)
    - Title XII (Box 8:, Folder 244)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture: International Science and Education Council, 1981-1986 (Box 8:, Folder 245)
  - Organization Files (Black Files)
    - Aetna Institute for Corporate Education (Box 8:, Folder 246)
    - Albertus Magnus College (Box 8:, Folder 247)
    - American Leadership Forum (Box 8:, Folder 248)
    - Bridgeport, University of (Box 8:, Folder 249)
    - Combined Health Appeal (Box 8:, Folder 250)
    - Connecticut Bank and Trust (Box 8:, Folder 251)
    - Connecticut State Grange (Box 8:, Folder 252)
    - Coopers and Lybrand (Box 8:, Folder 253)
    - Daigon, Ruth (Box 8:, Folder 254)
    - Endowed Chairs (Box 8:, Folder 255)
    - Graden, Dale (Box 8:, Folder 256)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box 8:, Folder 257)
    - Hartford Club (Box 8:, Folder 258)
    - Hartford, Consortium (Box 8:, Folder 259)
    - Hartford, University of (Box 8:, Folder 260)
    - Massachusetts, Commonwealth of (Box 8:, Folder 261)
    - Multiple Sclerosis Society (Box 8:, Folder 262)
    - New Jersey Department of Higher Education (Box 8:, Folder 263)
    - New York Times (Box 8:, Folder 264)
    - Petitti, Richard E. (Box 8:, Folder 265)
    - Questionnaires, Completed (Box 8:, Folder 266)
    - Quinnipiac College (Box 8:, Folder 267)
    - Research Corporation (Box 8:, Folder 268)
    - Stamford (Box 8:, Folder 269)
    - Science (Box 8:, Folder 270)
    - Shell Corporation (Box 8:, Folder 271)
    - Travelers Insurance (Box 8:, Folder 272)
    - University of Hartford (Box 8:, Folder 273)
    - U.S. News and World Report (Box 8:, Folder 274)
    - Wolff, Thomas J. (Box 8:, Folder 275)
    - Yale University (Box 8:, Folder 276)
  - Education Associations (Yellow Files)
    - A (Box 8:, Folder 277)
    - ACE (Box 8:, Folder 278)
    - C (Box 8:, Folder 279)
    - Council of Presidents (Box 8:, Folder 280-283)
    - NASULGC
      - 1985 (Box 8:, Folder 284)
      - 1984 (Box 8:, Folder 285)
      - ACE, Denver (November) (Box 8:, Folder 286)
      - Annual Meeting, Washington (November) (Box 8:, Folder 287)
      - Executive Committee (Box 8:, Folder 288)
    - National Center for Higher Education Management Systems (Box 8:, Folder 289)
    - New England Association of Schools and Colleges (Box 8:, Folder 290)
    - NEBHE (Box 8:, Folder 291)
- Series IV:, 1986
  - University Files (Red Files)
    - A (Box 9:, Folder 292)
    - Academic Affairs (Box 9:, Folder 293)
    - Accreditation (Box 9:, Folder 294-295)
    - Admissions (Box 9:, Folder 296)
    - Admissions: Property Considerations (Box 9:, Folder 297)
    - Admissions: Reports (Box 9:, Folder 298)
    - Admissions: Studies (Box 9:, Folder 299)
    - Affirmative Action: Move/Equipment Needs (Box 9:, Folder 300)
    - Affirmative Action Program (Box 9:, Folder 301-302)
    - Agriculture, College of (Box 9:, Folder 303)
    - Agriculture: Cooperative Extension Budget Cuts (Box 9:, Folder 304)
    - Agriculture: Holcomb Farm, Granby (Box 9:, Folder 305)
    - Alcohol Policy (Box 9:, Folder 306)
    - Allied Health (Box 9:, Folder 307)
    - Alumni, B - Z (Box 9:, Folder 308-327)
    - Alumni Association (Box 9:, Folder 328-329)
    - Alumni Association: Annual Fund (Box 9:, Folder 330)
    - Alumni Association: FAC Award for Excellence (Box 9:, Folder 331)
    - Alumni House (Box 9:, Folder 332)
    - Animal Care (Box 9:, Folder 333-334)
    - Annual Reports (Box 9:, Folder 335)
    - Anonymous Letters: Van Kruiningan (Box 9:, Folder 336)
    - Anthropology (Box 9:, Folder 337)
    - Art Department (Box 9:, Folder 338)
    - Assistant to the President: Galvin G. Hall (Box 9:, Folder 339)
    - Assistant to the President: Peter Halvorson (Box 9:, Folder 340)
    - Athletics (Box 9:, Folder 341-343)
      - AAPIA Academic Advising (Box 9:, Folder 344)
      - Annual Report (Box 9:, Folder 345)
      - Advisory Committee (Box 9:, Folder 346)
      - Academic Eligibility (Box 9:, Folder 347-348)
      - Basketball Coach Search (Box 9:, Folder 349)
      - Big East Conference (Box 9:, Folder 350)
      - Correspondence, External (Box 9:, Folder 351)
      - Development (Box 9:, Folder 352)
      - Drug Testing (Box 9:, Folder 353)
      - Intercollegiate Sports Cuts (Box 9:, Folder 354)
      - NCAA (Box 10:, Folder 355-357)
      - NCAA, New Orleans (January 13-15) (Box 10:, Folder 358)
      - Press Clips (Box 10:, Folder 359)
      - Project Planning Guide (Box 10:, Folder 360)
      - Recruitment by President (Box 10:, Folder 361)
      - Sports Center (Box 10:, Folder 362)
      - Sports Center Presentation (February 11) (Box 10:, Folder 363)
      - Task Force on Athletics (Box 10:, Folder 364-376)
      - Yankee Conference (Box 10:, Folder 377)
    - Attorney (Box 10:, Folder 378)
    - Audit Subcommittee (Box 10:, Folder 379)
    - Auditor
      - Activity Report (Box 10:, Folder 380)
      - Board of Trustees Audit Subcommittee (Box 10:, Folder 381)
      - Daily Campus (see also Student Organizations) (Box 10:, Folder 382)
      - Education Psychology (School of Education) (Box 10:, Folder 383)
        Scope and Contents note
        (see also Lawsuits, Rickards)
      - Grants and Contracts (Box 10:, Folder 384)
      - Health Center (Box 10:, Folder 385)
      - Personnel (Box 10:, Folder 386)
      - Regional Campus Café Committee (Box 10:, Folder 387)
      - Research Foundation: Overhead Recoveries (Box 10:, Folder 388)
      - Search Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 10:, Folder 389)
      - Staff Vacancy, 1986-1987 (Box 10:, Folder 390)
      - UConn League (Box 10:, Folder 391)
    - B (Box 10:, Folder 392)
    - Barney House (Box 10:, Folder 393)
    - Biobehavioral Science: Funding, and Research (Box 10:, Folder 394)
    - Biology (Box 10:, Folder 395)
    - Biotechnology (Box 10:, Folder 396)
    - Black Studies, Center for (Box 10:, Folder 397)
    - Bloodmobile (Box 10:, Folder 398)
    - Budget (Box 11:, Folder 399)
    - Budget: January - July (Box 11:, Folder 400-402)
    - Budget: vacancy count/shortfall (Box 11:, Folder 403)
    - Burke, Fred (Box 11:, Folder 404)
    - Bursar (Box 11:, Folder 405)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 11:, Folder 406)
    - Business Administration, School of: Brochures (Box 11:, Folder 407)
    - Business Administration, School of: Connecticut Small Business Development Center (Box 11:, Folder 408)